Dawson Vo

TORONTO, ONTARIO (647) 620-3290 VO.DAWSONLC@GMAIL.COM

Undergraduate Dean's List Scholar, currently studying at Ryerson University towards a computer science major. Has been responsible for leading school wide events, EASA film team, and York Memorial Tech team, as well as helping with fundraisers and festivals. Highly energetic and approachable and with great communication skills.

SKILLS AND ABILITIES

- Flexible and able to adapt easily
- Proactive and Self-Starter Attitude
- Advanced problem-solving/troubleshooting skills
- Familiar with object-oriented programming
- Strong desire to learn
- Computer hardware proficient
- Proficient with Microsoft Office Suite
- Languages: Java, Python, C, Visual Basic, Bash

EDUCATION

Ryerson University

Bachelor of Science (Honours), Computer Science – (Co-op)

- CGPA: 3.95
- Expected graduation date: June 2023

York Memorial C.I.

Ontario Secondary School Diploma

Toronto, Ontario

September 2018 – Present

Toronto, Ontario

September 2014 – June 2018

WORK EXPERIENCE

Canadian National Exhibition – C.N.E.

18-Day Staff (Admission Ticket Seller/Cashier)

- Efficiently and accurately handled cash and card transaction in fast-paced work environment
- Worked both independently and collaboratively with other ticker booth sellers

Williams Sonoma

Seasonal staff member (Cashier & Stockroom Associate)

- Completed up to 150 sales transactions a day, and assisted in moving product to
- Answered customer inquiries in person and over the phone
- Organized and kept inventory of stock and showroom

Pho Com 99

Part-time staff member (Cashier, Server & Dishwasher)

- Comfortable in fast-paced work environments
- Proficient in handling cash and card transactions
- Skillfully handled catering up to 5 tables at a time maintaining company standards

Toronto, Ontario August 2019 – September 2019

Toronto, Ontario September 2018 – January 2019

Mississauga, Ontario January 2016 - April 2018

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

TDSB - 160 Hours

Computer Management

- Upgraded ~200 lab computers within the school
- Repaired and maintained all computers in the school to ensure peak performance
- Added networking infrastructure for the connection of more machines to the internet

Student Helper

- Helped teach 20 students that were taking computer science on a one-to-one
- Carried out tasks for teachers to gather supplies, set up project displays
- Arranged and divided learning material for students

Toronto, Ontario *February 2015 – June 2018*

EXTRA-CURRICULAR

Stage Crew October 2016 – June 2018

• Set up audio equipment and managed up to 5 crew members for 10 school events

- Editor and Cinematographer for all school event recordings
- Some annual events include; EASA Assembly, Black History Month, Developmentally Delayed Students Field Day, Encore

East Asian Student Association (EASA)

October 2015 – January 2018

- Editor and Cinematographer for Martial Arts Short Film
- Fundraised and managed financial during a school event

ACHIEVEMENTS

Faculty of Science Dean's List

May 2019

Honour Rolls September 2012 - June 2018

AP Physics Award November 2017

AP Psychology Award November 2017